export const Questions = [
  { questionNo: 1, question: 'What number is after 22, 23, ... ', answer: 24, hint: 'Add 1' },
  { questionNo: 2, question: 'What number is after 10, 20, ... ', answer: 30, hint: 'Add 10' },
  { questionNo: 3, question: 'What number is after 2, 4, ... ', answer: 6, hint: 'Add 2'},
  { questionNo: 4, question: 'What number is after 10, 8, ... ', answer: 6, hint: 'Minus 2' },
  { questionNo: 5, question: 'What number is after 16, 17, ... ', answer: 18, hint: 'Add 1' },
  { questionNo: 6, question: 'What number is after 6, 7, ... ', answer: 8, hint: 'Add 1' },
  { questionNo: 7, question: 'What number is after 22, 23, ... ', answer: 24, hint: 'Add 1' },
  { questionNo: 8, question: 'What number is after 10, 20, ... ', answer: 30, hint: 'Add 10' },
  { questionNo: 9, question: 'What number is after 2, 4, ... ', answer: 6, hint: 'Add 2'},
  { questionNo: 10, question: 'What number is after 10, 8, ... ', answer: 6, hint: 'Minus 2' },
  { questionNo: 11, question: 'What number is after 16, 17, ... ', answer: 18, hint: 'Add 1' },
  { questionNo: 12, question: 'What number is after 6, 7, ... ', answer: 8, hint: 'Add 1' },
]
